<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deploy Overwatch on Overwatch</title>
    <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/deployoverwatch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deploy Overwatch on Overwatch</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 18:31:01 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/deployoverwatch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline Validation</title>
      <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/deployoverwatch/pipelinevalidation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/deployoverwatch/pipelinevalidation/</guid>
      <description>Overview Overwatch provides a special pipeline validation module to perform a number of data quality, data completeness, and referential integrity checks on its output. Pipeline validation may run as frequently as the regularly scheduled, automated Overwatch ETL pipeline runs/deployments or manually as a notebook command. It is used by the Overwatch maintainers to guard against data quality regressions when extending and enhancing Overwatch&amp;rsquo;s internal logic. Similarly, we are encouraging users to apply this tool to their deployments to provide data quality readouts and to assist with customer issue resolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Overwatch Data</title>
      <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/deployoverwatch/sharingoverwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 18:31:01 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/deployoverwatch/sharingoverwatch/</guid>
      <description>Granting Access Via DBSQL If your storage prefix is referencing a mount point, nothing should be necessary here as the mount point is already accessible to all workspace users. If using a direct path (i.e. s3://, abfss://, or gs://) you will need to configure the appropriate access in Admin Settings &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; SQL Warehouse Settings.&#xA;If using a Hive Metastore you may still need to review your grants to ensure users have access to the Overwatch tables / views.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
