<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on Overwatch</title>
    <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/gettingstarted/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on Overwatch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:40:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/gettingstarted/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/gettingstarted/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 11:55:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/gettingstarted/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Configuration Basics The Overwatch configuration can be created as a case class of OverwatchParams or as a json string passed into the main class com.databricks.labs.overwatch.BatchRunner. When passed in as a json string, it is serialized into an instance of OverwatchParams. This provides strong validation on the input parameters and strong typing for additional validation options. All configs attempt to be defaulted to a reasonable default where possible. If a default is set, passing in a value will overwrite the default.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modules</title>
      <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/gettingstarted/modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/gettingstarted/modules/</guid>
      <description>Modules Modules are the method by which Overwatch is segmented; currently, the modules available include:
 audit clusters clusterEvents pools jobs accounts notebooks DBSQL sparkEvents  The default is to use all modules so if none are specified in the configuration, all modules will be enabled. Currently, under normal, daily operations, there no significant cost to any of these modules. It&amp;rsquo;s likely best to leave them all turned on unless there&amp;rsquo;s a specific reason not to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Topics</title>
      <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/gettingstarted/advancedtopics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 13:43:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/gettingstarted/advancedtopics/</guid>
      <description>Quick Reference  Externalize Optimize &amp;amp; Z-Order Interacting With Overwatch and its State Joining With Slow Changing Dimensions (SCD) Optimizing Overwatch  Optimizing Overwatch Expectation Check Note that Overwatch analyzes nearly all aspects of the Workspace and manages its own pipeline among many other tasks. This results in 1000s of spark job executions and as such, the Overwatch job will take some time to run. For small/medium workspaces, 20-40 minutes should be expected for each run.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
