<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Engineering on Overwatch</title>
    <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/dataengineer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Engineering on Overwatch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 08:47:24 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/dataengineer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline_Management</title>
      <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/dataengineer/pipeline_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 12:21:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/dataengineer/pipeline_management/</guid>
      <description>Overwatch Data Promotion Process Overwatch data is promoted from bronze - silver - gold - presentation to ensure data consistency and quality as the data is enriched between the stages. The presentation layer is composed of views that reference the latest schema version of the gold layer. This disconnects the consumption layer from the underlying data structure so that developers can transparently add and alter columns without user disruption. All tables in each layer (except consumption) are suffixed in the ETL database with _layer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/dataengineer/upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 21:27:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/dataengineer/upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes upgrading from one version to the next requires a schema change. In these cases, the CHANGELOG will be explicit. Upgrades MUST be executed WITH the new library (jar) and before the pipeline is executed. The general upgrade process is:
 Use the compactString of parameters to instantiate the workspace  The compact string can be found in your original runner notebook which you got from here   Call the upgrade function for the version to which you&amp;rsquo;re upgrading and pass in the workspace object  Basic pseudocode can be found below as a reference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productionizing</title>
      <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/dataengineer/productionizing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 15:03:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/dataengineer/productionizing/</guid>
      <description>Moving To Production When you&amp;rsquo;re ready to move to production, there are a few things to keep in mind and best practices to follow to get the most out of Overwatch
Cluster Logging Simplify and Unify your cluster logging directories
 Many users forget to enable cluster logging and without it Overwatch cannot provide usage telemetry by notebook, job, user so it&amp;rsquo;s critical that all clusters have clusters logs enabled If users are allowed to create clusters/jobs without any governance, log files will be produced and stored all over the place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
