<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Environment Setup on Overwatch</title>
    <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/environmentsetup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Environment Setup on Overwatch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 05:49:17 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/environmentsetup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure</title>
      <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/environmentsetup/azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:12:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/environmentsetup/azure/</guid>
      <description>Configuring Overwatch on Azure Databricks Reference Architecture Configuring Audit Log Delivery Through Event Hub Setting up Storage Accounts Mount Storage Accounts  Configuring Overwatch on Azure Databricks Reach out to your Customer Success Engineer (CSE) to help you with these tasks as needed. To get started, the Basic Deployment configuration. As more modules are enabled, additional environment configuration may be required in addition to the Basic Deployment.
There are two primary sources of data that need to be configured:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS</title>
      <link>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/environmentsetup/aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:12:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://databrickslabs.github.io/overwatch/environmentsetup/aws/</guid>
      <description>Configuring Overwatch on AWS - Databricks Reach out to your Customer Success Engineer (CSE) to help you with these tasks as needed. To get started, the Basic Deployment configuration. As more modules are enabled, additional environment configuration may be required in addition to the Basic Deployment.
There are two primary sources of data that need to be configured:
 Audit Logs  These will be delivered to the configured bucket. These buckets are configured on a per-workspace basis and can be delivered to the same target bucket, just ensure that the prefixes are different to avoid collisions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
